A Guide to the Robert N. Giaimo Papers 1980.0003
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series XI: Guest and Appointment Books, 1959-1980
  - Office Guest Books, 1970-1980; (7 vols) (Box 268)
  - Reception Guest Books, 1964-1976; (6 vols) (Box 269)
  - Gallery Passes Book, undated
  - Appointment Books, 1959-1980; (22 vols) (Box 270)
- Series XII: Scrapbooks, 1956-1978
  - 1956 (Box 271)
  - 1958 (Box 272)
  - 1959 (Box 273)
  - 1960 (Box 274)
  - 1961 (Box 275)
  - 1962 (Box 276)
  - 1963-1964 (Box 277)
  - 1964-1966 (Box 278)
  - 1966-1967 (Box 279)
  - 1967-1968 (Box 280)
  - 1968-1969 (Box 281)
  - 1969-1970 (Box 282)
  - 1970 (Box 283)
  - 1970-1971 (Box 284)
  - 1971-1972 (Box 285)
  - 1972-1973 (Box 286)
  - 1973-1974 (Box 287)
  - 1974-1975 (Box 288)
  - 1976 (Box 289)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 290)
  - 1978 (Box 291)
  - 1956-1970 (Box 292)
  - (Elections), 1960-1977 (Box 293)
  - 1971-1975 (Box 294)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 295)